[music]
[音楽]
piece
ピース
Good evening, today is Minecraft
こんばんは今日はマイクラ
It's so bad, I've only been eating oden every day lately.
ですやばいここ最近毎日おでんしか食べてない
Wow today is seven
わ今日はセブン
oden deko and chia egg
のおでんでコとチア卵
Only Chiabu is not that Chikuwa.
だけえチアブってあのちくわじゃないんだ
What is Nechikuwabu?
ねちくわブってあれ何
What kind of person is talking about holding a pot?
持ちなべちゃべちゃしてるやつはいなんなん
It's white and sticky, like hearsay.
だじゃ白くてもちもちしてる伝聞みたい
It's Nabu. I'm sorry, I don't know what Bu is.
なブですよ何ブってごめんいや知ら
No, no, but
ないいやでも
I'm not talking about Nechooden, but I usually only sleep on my stomach.
ねちょおでんの話じゃないんだけど僕普段からうつ伏せでしか寝れないっ
That's what I said. Good luck today. It's probably my first time trying to sleep properly on my back.
て言ってたじゃん今日頑張ってね初めてえ多分なんかちゃんと仰向けで寝ようと
It's the first time I've been able to sleep with this in mind. It's okay for everyone to lie on their backs today.
思って寝れたの初めてだよな今日みんな仰向けはいい
It was amazing. It was hard to sleep, but I tried my best to sleep on my back.
ぞすごいね寝るの大変だったんだけど頑張って仰向けで寝てみたらなん
And I wake up feeling really good.
と寝起きがめちゃくちゃ良くて
And I never had nightmares. When I dream, I definitely see demons.
かつ悪夢を見なかった夢見る時絶対悪魔見るんだよ
I've had nightmares on any given day, but today is not a nightmare.
どんな日でも悪夢を見てきたんだけど今日はね悪夢じゃなかっ
I don't remember what I dreamed about, but I'll do my best and turn around from now on.
た何の夢を見たか覚えてないけどいやちょっと頑張ってこれから仰向き
I thought about sleeping in
で寝ようと思った
Well, I guess it has something to do with sleeping. Lying on your stomach makes you more likely to have nightmares.
ねいや多分ねそうなんか寝を関係あるらしいうつ伏せはね悪夢を見やすいんだっ
I heard that I'm playing Pokemon Sleep, and right now I'm making a selection of Eve and Gorse.
てそ聞いたポケモンスリープやってるやってるよ今はねイーブとゴースの厳選をし
A selection that never ends
てる全然終わんない厳選
Later, Yasuya appears.
があとすやすやが出
Pokemon sleep is divided into three types: nap, sleep, and sound sleep.
ないなんかポケモンスリープってうとうとすやすやぐっすりのなんか3種類に分け
I can do it, but most of the time I'm sleeping soundly or dozing off.
られるんだけど寝てるパターンが大体ぐっすりかウトウですやすやがマジで出
It's not there, how can I get it out?
ないんだよどうやったら出るんだよすやすや
That's why I can't catch fire type Pokemon.
そうだから僕炎タイプのポケモン捕まえられないんだ
There's a strict selection of personalities and skills for Pokemon Sleep, and it all depends on that.
よポケモンスリープ厳やるなんか性格とかスキル厳選があってそれによって全然ね
The points are different, so the higher the points, the rarer Pokemon you can get.
ポイントが違うんだよでポイントが高ければ高いほどやっぱレアなポケモンとかも出
You can go to places where it gets easier, and it's pretty deep.Pokémon Sweep
やすくなるところに行けるし結構ね深いんですよポケモンスイープ
I finally reached level 21. I'm a level 37 Pokemon.
はやっと21レベになったほお僕はね37レベだよポケモン
I'm a big fan of sleep, so this is my first time using Pokemon Sleep.
スリープガチ勢だからとりあえずねポケモンスリープ初めの
I think people should choose Butterfree instead of Eve.
人はねみんなイブじゃなくてあのバタフリーを厳選するといい
Yo Butterfree is seriously the strongest, so when I first started, I had two Butterfrees.
よバタフリーマジ最強だから僕最初の頃はバタフリー2体構成にし
There were two Butterfrees, Golduck, Raichu, and Windy.
てたよバタフリー2体とゴルダックとライチュとあとウィンディがね
It's not listed on any strategy site, but it's Windy Maji.
最強どこの攻略サイトにも載ってないけどウィンディマジで
I see a lot of people saying that the strongest Windy is normal, but for me, Windy is probably the best.
最強ウィンディは普通ですみたいなところ結構見るんだけど僕的にねウィンディ多分
Netia Zetia S number 1
ねティアゼティアSです1番
Upper Windy is a skill that helps other Pokemon.
上ウィンディってスキルが他のポケモンにお手伝いするっていう効果なんだ
But that's serious
けどそれがねマジで
The strongest is so-so, so today it's Minecraft.
最強まあまあまあということで今日はマイクラです
Well, first of all, let me explain the project.Eko's listener participation type project.This is me.
さてじゃ最初に企画の説明をするとえこのリスナー参加型の企画こちら僕が
A plan to build anything you like inside the cat's square base that you have prepared.
用意したねこの真四角の土台の中に好きなように建築をしようっていう企画
So it's my third week this week, so let's see how far I've come.
で今週で3周目になりましたさあどこまで行ったでしょうか見ていき
Because it's Mashooi
ましょうおいということで
Please give me flowers. I've opened a flower shop. That's why I log in every day.
ください僕のお花お花屋さんができましたそう僕もなんだかんだでね毎日ログイン
I've been making it from time to time.
してちょこちょこと作ってはいるんです
Yoko Nene also copied the building next door, but it's a complete copy.
よこですねもこの隣の建築パクったんだけど完全に丸パクりです
I built a flower shop next to the cat's fish shop without permission.
ねこのお魚屋さんの隣にお花屋さんを勝手に作りまし
This is a really nice block, but I think it could be used for a stylish shop.
たこれめっちゃいいブロックじゃないなんかいおしゃれなお店に使えるなと思っ
This is a seriously stylish blog.
てやってみたこれガチおしゃれおしゃれブロだ
This is my ideal flower shop.It's really nice.
よこれ僕の理想のねお花屋さんですなかなかいい
So, let's look at it as a whole.
でしょということでさて全体的に見た
But what has changed is that there is no longer a place where everyone can make it.
けど変わったところもうだいぶなんかみんなね作れるところないなって状態に
I see, you can just make the top part, just make sure to fill in all the gaps.
なってるでしょもう上とか作っていいからね本当に隙間を全部ね埋めるようにして
I want it, and I'm thinking of destroying it all.
欲しいんだよ僕ははということであもあれ壊そうと思ってん
But I made it randomly, but I'm going to destroy it.That's that huge tunnel I made.
だけど適当に作ってましたでも壊しますあれあのでかいトンネルね作ったんだけど
I seriously can't think of a use for it, there are so many hidden routes.
使い道がマジで思い浮かばないそう裏裏ルートが多すぎてじゃぱっと
If you look at the places where the number of people watching has increased, I really like it.Fill in the gaps.
見なんか増えたなみたいなところを見ていくかあいいねなんか本当にね隙間を埋め
I want it like this
て欲しいんだよこんな感じに
And
とか
Oh man, I was looking forward to this. It's not done yet. This is terrible.
おおいやこれ楽しみにしてたんだよなまだできてないなこれやばく
No, I think it's probably an SCP facility, but the Foundation is serious about this.
ない多分SCPの施設だと思うけど財団これマジで
This is an enchanted room that's starting to look pretty good.
やばいあでもなんかだいぶできてきてるエンチャント部屋だ
Something is starting to get done quite a bit.
だいぶなんかできてきてるよねあ
That's right, this is it
そうこおおこれ
is a toilet
はトイレ
This is so nice
だこれはおいいね
You really worked hard on the stairs.
階段これ頑張ってんなマジ
dekoko
でここ
The flies are amazing
はえすごうわ
Wow, this is a containment breach. It's seriously a containment breach. I'm calling B here.
すごいこれ収容違反をきてるよガチで収容違反をきてるここでビーって
Do it, this is amazing
やるんだねこれすごい
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
なこっちはあえいいじゃんいいじゃんいい
Jan Foundation Staff
じゃん財団のねスタッフ
This place is a big man's home.
のあいなここはねお偉いさんのねとこ
What is it being used for?
だよいしょいやこっから何がね使用されて
I'm looking forward to seeing you there.There's a reference room here and there.
いくのか楽しみだなここはあここも資料室だえこんな
There was a block, this is paro, this is seriously amazing
ブロックあったんだこれパロこれマジですごいわ
This is without a shadow, so this is also this server, and if you add a shadow,
これ影モなしでこれだからねもこのサーバーね影も入れると
You made it because the amount of blocks had increased to the point where it was extremely heavy.
めちゃくちゃ重くなるレベルにブロックの量が多くなってしまったからお君が作った
You can go check out Kacho's upper floor.
のかちょ上の階見に行ってみていい
It's so well made it's a big deal
かガチ作り込まれてるおおこっからかえ
What's amazing is that not all rooms have the same feel, but each room has its own unique feel.
えすごいななんか全部同じ感じじゃなくて1つ1つの部屋こだわりが
Guide me by feeling
感じる案内して
I just came to see Kururu, so I guess he'll show me around.
くれる見に来ただけあ案内してくれるっぽい
No, white matter, what is this?
なうん白質ねええ何これえこれ
Wow, this is the first time I've seen this.
何すごこんなの初めて見
They're working really hard on this duct.
たわ頑張ってんなこのダクトのところとか
I got something amazing, but I probably couldn't pick it up.
すげえんなんかもらったけど拾えなかったな多分
It's probably a block on the floor below.
下の床のブロックだろう
In Nahon
なほんで
Archive Komada?
アーカイブここまだか
This is World Elite. Only I can use it. Other people can't use it.
なこれねワールドエリットね入れてあの僕だけ使える他の人はね使えない
Condition
状態お
Please enter your authentication information below.
下ほんほんほんほんほんえ認証情報入力して
Please Pio Entry Log
くださいピおおエントリーログ
Welcome to the collection of temporary site 98, which has been certified.
認証受け付けしました臨時サイト98の収画へようこそ
Amazing parentheses
すげえかっこ
Go ahead and go
いい行ってき
It's starting to double
ますこっから二重になっ
Teru
てる
a
あ
Wait a minute, I don't know, I'll see later
はちょっと待って知らない後で見ようまたクソでか建築できてんだけど後
Let's take a look at that. It's the Back Rooms, right? The Back Rooms are also expanding day by day.
で見ようあれだってバックルームズでしょバックルームズもなんか日々拡大されてる
It's spreading more and more
んだよどんどん広がっ
What's above
てる上のなん
It's amazing that things like Futoshi are being built here and there.
だ富年みたいなのができてるすごすぎるあここら辺も
It makes me sleepy
ねなるほどなるほど
I'm really looking forward to this and other things at a glance.
いや楽しみだなここもま他パッと見の
However, I haven't been able to do anything like this.
ところこれなんかできてん
I guess it's still a legend
なあまだ伝説途中かな
No, it looks like an amazing garden that has already been built.
いやなんかもうできてるすごい庭園みたいになっ
I wonder if he's doing it by himself. It's really scary.
てる声1人でやってんのかなやばいなマジ
I saw something like Deyosu.A little while after I saw another outrageous thing.
でよすなんか見てしまったまた別のとんでもないの見てしまったちょっと後で
Let's go see it too
見に行こうあれもはあ
Aine Izakaya Ramen
あいいね居酒屋ラーメン
Well, everyone is doing well without world editing.
といやみんなワールドエディットなしでよく頑張ってる
You're trying too hard
よ頑張りすぎだ
This is really bad, I saw this place like 000 and Spirited Away before.
よやばいなあえねなんか本当に000と治療の神隠しみたいなここだって前見た
Look ahead here
もんなここは前見て
No, it's getting bigger and bigger
いやどんどんでかくなっ
Teruhon is a little better or something like that.
てるほんでちょ上行くかまあそことか
Hey, if I recall correctly, you made that casino casino before, right?
ねあで確かあれカジノカジノなんか前作ってたよねあれ
What do you think? Is it finished?
どうだろう出来上がったんか
What are you doing? I'll do it later.
なやってるやってるちょ後にするか
casino
カジノ
Something is being done here again.
ここあまた何かできてるなん
Wow, it's a bit of an edgy venue.
だうわあなんかちょっとエッジな会場だわ
School Swimsuit Cocoa also has a shop like that, and this is probably a shop like that.
スク水ここそういうお店もしてここはもしかしてそういうお店です
sit and watch
か座って見る
of
の
Wow pole dancing
うわあポールダンスのし
bread
パン
Wow, this is a sensitive shop.
すげえこれセンシティブなお店だ
It was done before I knew it.
いつの間にかできてるいやあれ
Maybe that or that game I did in collaboration.
かもしかしてあれかあの僕がやったコラボでやったあのゲーム
That's amazing, that's an art museum, isn't it?
のすげえあであれが美術館だよねそういえ
I saw this player from Bacochcha. A nice house has been built.
ばこちっちゃのねこれ選手見ましたあいいね家ができてき
Teruko's stylish house. Maybe you haven't seen this.
てるこおしゃれなねお家これ見てないかも
Na Hotel Grand Shini Na Shini Naa 427 My Birthday
なホテルグランシニなシニなあ427僕の誕生日
Neo
ねお
Stylish things are great, Viking Daiyappa bread
おしゃれあこれいいじゃんバイキングだいやっぱパン
That scenery outside is scary
よこの景色あれ怖い
Is there a room at Naja Hotel?
なじゃホテルの部屋もあるかな
Underground too
お地下も
No, I want a pool, I'm in the process of building one.
あるいやプール欲しいなあ作ってる途中
I'm bothering you, this is it
だこお邪魔しますおおこれ
This restaurant has a more luxurious feel.
レストラントこっちの方が高級感あるなこのは
This is my first time seeing you. I came from a clipping. Welcome.
おこっちは初見です切抜から来ましたいらっしゃい
I'm watching this week's edition.
今見てます今週分を見てい
I'd like to build a pool if I can stay here.
ますここまだかいやせっかくならプールも作ってほしい
No, this and that
ないいぞあれこれカ
The head of the awesome wither skeleton is now
道楽すごいウィザースケルトンの頭はになっ
This is amazing.
てるこれすごくねこれや
It's a stupid hobby
ばカ道楽だ
Sea urchin and
ウニや
A high quality live show came.
ばクオリティ高ライブ来た
I wonder if Starry was made.During construction, things are starting to take shape.
スターリーできたかなあ工事中あでもなんか形になってき
I'm really looking forward to it
てるすげえ楽しみ
Didn't you see Amo in Dahon? I saw that too.
だほんであも見てないかあいやあれ見た
Kakoko
かここ
Nehon
ねほん
So this is also added
であここも追加され
octopus chinese style
たこの中華スタイルの
Hey, it's okay, it's okay
ねおいいじゃんいい
Jan
じゃん
Ah, there are many kinds of architecture that have a unique feel.
ああオンリーアップ感あるやばなんかいろんな建築がある
After all, I didn't do Only Up.
から結局僕オンリーアップやってないもん
There is also a tatami room
なお畳の部屋も
That's nice.
あるいいねああな
Oh, I can see how it's just growling here.
おおここうなってるだけかなるほど
They don't sell it anymore, so I bought it the day they stopped selling it.
ねもう売ってないしな僕ね買ったんだよ販売しなくなったその日に買ったんだよ
I bought it on the very unlucky day when sales were suspended.
めっちゃ運良くない販売停止の日に買っ
Ta
た
Oh, there's something suspicious here. There's something behind this.
おおなんか怪しげなここ何かあるぞこれ裏に何かある
Zohoraada
ぞほらあだ
But I can't go any further.
けど先は行けないなここまで
I'm going to hide it. I'm going to hide my listener. I don't know where anything is.
かいや隠すからなうちのリスナー隠すからねどこに何があるか分からないん
is
だ
I want to be able to go there on foot someday.
よいずれはこうやってあの徒歩で行けるようにしたい
I can't go, I'll have to walk
ねこれ行けないやん徒歩
I'm releasing this save data for sightseeing who wants to be able to go all on foot.
で徒歩で全部行けるようにしたい観光用にこのセーブデータを公開する
It's scheduled so the general public can enter.
予定だから一般の人が入れるよう
to
に
Oh this is here
おおここはあ
It's been here for a long time, but there's no interior yet.
出れるでここずっとあるけど未だ内装はないんだよ
Nakocchihato
なこっちはと
I saw something like a huge castle just now.
かなんかさっきでかい城みたいの見えた
Ken 3D Studio
けどん3Dスタジオ
oh
おお
amazing 3d studio
すごい3Dスタジオ
You can cut out only here with a green bag.
だここでみ切り抜きができるよグリーンバッグで
this
これ
Wow this is interesting
すごいこれ面白い
A space where you can climb with a ne
ねで登れるスペ
There's a shopping street.
ん商店街なんかあるな
Oh, it's done, it's done, it's Matsuya, it's Matsuya.
おおできてるできてる松屋あ松屋だ
I saw a video of someone walking into Matsuya and leaving after 30 seconds of eating something at home.
すごなんか松屋入って30秒で家なんかご飯食べて出るみたいな動画見たなこの
The front is cute, this kind of logistics is nice behind the scenes
前わいいこういうロジ裏いい
This is what I was looking for
なこういうのよ求めてたものを
scared
怖い
That's a figure
なフィギあれ
I can't help but feel like this is Coulomb.
ねなるほどねこれぞクーロンて感じするよ
Neyoshi
ねよし
Okay, yes, yes, yes, shutter.
よしあはいはいはいはいシャッター
You can fill in the gaps with things like this and more like this.
ガこういうのこういうのもっとこういうねところ隙間埋めていい
That's why it doesn't matter what kind of architecture you want.
んだからねみんなどんな建築でもいいからだってあれ
It's safe enough that there are
がいるぐらいだよ安全
Daichi, do you want to go see the casino?
大地ほんじゃあカジノ見に行くか
See the casino at the casino
カジノでカジノ見
Then go to the middle and go to the person who will introduce you this time.
たら真ん中行って今回紹介してくれる人のところ行く
Oh wait, there's one above too
かあ待って上もある
It's an alien! They're being caught.
な宇宙人だあ捕まってるとれのろ捕まっ
It's like an alien
てる宇宙人にってる
How do I get in here?
よどうやって入るんだこれ
I can't enter the lottery
抽選入れないの
Is this a cloud? It's a cloud's house.
かこれ雲かな雲の家だ
What are you looking at? This place is dangerous.
なこれ見るかいやここやばいよ
Well done
なよくやったよ
Come on, I'm turning into a bunny because last week I told you to turn into a bunny.
お来たあバニーになってる僕は先週バニーにしろって言ったから
Now that I'm Vanine, I'd like you to introduce me.
バニーヌになってるさて紹介してもらおうかなじゃあ
I can't play Ecoin, I'm really in the middle of this
えコイン遊べんのこれで本当にこ真ん中
What, this is seriously amazing
何いやこれマジすごいよ
There is a guidebook on how to play Nae Roulette.
なえルーレット遊び方ガイドブックがあるこれ
Roulette: Put a coin into the yellow box and press the center button to start. If you win, the game will turn purple.
ルーレットえ黄色い箱にコインを入れて中心のボタンを押すとスタート当たれば紫
twice the number you put in the box.
の箱に入れた数の2倍の
I see, I put the coin in the yellow box, but what if it's purple? Really?
え黄色い箱にコインを入れるあなるほどなるほどで紫じゃどうしよっかなえ本当に
I guess I'll do it here then.
じゃここにしよっかな
Okay, let's go with 32 switches.
じゃあ32個よし行くぜスイッチ
On amazing
オンすご
My carp is gone
は僕のコイはあなくなっ
Just one more time, 16 pieces.
たもう1回16個だ
I guess there are a lot of people who don't get it right at all.
来いは全然当たんないこっちが多いのなんか
here this
こここれ
Na
な
Yes, it's a shame
はい惜しいうわ
It's a shame, I don't get it at all, but I feel like this is the only place here
惜しい全然当たんねいやでもここばっかな気するここ
Let's put this and this three together 3
とこことこの3つかけにしようこ3
Hey [music]
ね[音楽]
It came true
け来当たった
That manager doesn't have any money, it's my money.
あれお支配人金ないぞ僕の金
I can't give it back
返せえ違っ
Tao is gone
たおなくなっちゃっ
I don't have any octopus, I just bought one more
たコンないよもう1個強えたん
Or maybe it's a bug. That's amazing.
かバグかもいやすごい
Yo, this is a money exchange place.
よこれはあ換金所だふわもらっ
Toko
とこう
amazing slots
すごいスロット
There are also nice bars in the area.
エリアあこれいいねバーも
It's so nice that it makes me want to play an MMO.When I see something like this, I want to play slots.
あるわいいななんかMMOやりたくなるねこういうの見るとスロット
Oh no, I can't even do this. I can play this too.
えまさかこれもできんのこれも遊べる
Well, I managed to win one.
じゃあえ1個あえ当たった
It was amazing1
すごいよった1
This is no good, this isn't bad.
個これダなんねえこれやばくない
Yes, I'm sorry I broke it, I broke it.
はいこだねごめん壊しちゃったやばい壊しちゃった
Are you okay?
大丈夫かこれこし
I'm sorry, I'm healed, Silka Box.
てあやばい私治った配にごめんシルカボックス
I broke it and couldn't open it.
壊しちゃった開けられなくなってた
Well, it's okay
えこれ大丈夫
Ah, thank you, 8 coins.
あありがとうよし8コインあはは来
Receive 22 Tasugee
たすげえ22個もらえ
Takore is really interesting
たこれめっちゃ面白い
Well, you can earn coins for the rest of your life.
じゃんこれ一生コイン稼げるな
It's not bad that it came out as if it was a confirmed performance.
えなんか確定演出みたいな出たのやばくない
Nice, this is so perfect.
ナイス何これこれの完成度高すぎ
Right, I'm still planning on making something else. What is this?
でしょえまだ他にわ作ってる予定だなえこれ何これ
teeth
は
Eahahahaha
えあはははは
Yes, yes, it's pinball. Yes, this is difficult.
はいはいピンボールだはいこれむずいって
Let's do this together, okay, this is interesting.
これ2人でやりよだはいはいここ面白い
What is this float? What is this float? Seriously?
なてかこの浮は何この浮は何マジで
Yes, yes, I'm only going to the middle, but okay.
はいはいあ真ん中ばっか行くんだけどはいよし
Okay
よし
First of all, yes, yes, yes, I have to do it properly.
まずはいはいはいはいちゃんとやんなきゃ跳ね
I can't change it, yes, yes, yes.
かえないなはいはいはいはい
Yes yes no
はいはいや
Even if you do this, you won't get any coins or anything.
ばこれでもなんかあれかコインもらえるとかはない
ka [music]
か[音楽]
This is genius
これ天才
That's amazing. This is seriously amazing.
でしょすごいなこれマジすごいないや
Circuit Karokume's hand that I really respect
回路カロくめの本当に尊敬する手札手札
Hey, what is this? It's a rulebook. When you press the button at your feet, you get 1 card.
へこれは何あルールブックだポカ来た足元のボタン押すとカードが1
It will go into the blue box on the right.Press the button in order.Multiple places at the same time.
枚右えっと青い箱に入りますふんふんふんボタン順番に押してください複数箇所同時
If you press it, it may not work properly.To exchange cards, discard the cards in the red box on the left, and then press the red box on the left for that many cards.
に押すとうまく動かないかもカード交換は左の赤い箱にカードを捨ててその枚数分
Please press the button again. Cards when you are finished playing.
またボタンを押してください遊び終わったらカード
Put them all in a red box, shuffle them using the lever on the table, and after a few seconds, press the lever.
を全て赤い箱に入れてテーブル上のレバーでシャッフルして何秒か経ったらレバーを
Turn it off and turn on the lever on the right for about 5 seconds.The deck is out and no cards come out.
切って右のレバーを5秒ほどオンにしてください山札切れでカードが出ない
Hahahaha Even if the foot lamp in front of you is out, use any procedure to return the card to the deck.
はふはふ正面手前の足元ランプが切れている時もどの手順でカードを山札に戻せ
Masuhonhonhonhon
ますほんほんほん
Well, first of all, this?
えっとまずこれか
Ho
ほ
2 spades in the middle of the spade
でこん中にはいスペードの2スペードの
How many cards are there in 2 poker? [Music]
2でえ何枚だっけポーカーって[音楽]
How many Poka are there?
ポカって何枚もう1
Okay, okay, 5 or 25 times.
回5枚か25枚オケーオケ
I can't find the orchestra
オケあてない
Na1
な1
Shea Akita Ert Club 2
枚あ来たえっとクラブの2
A different diamond
あ違うダイヤ
Kamada Kanahoi Club
かまだかなほいクラブの
4 of 5 clubs is weak
5クラブの4いやちょ弱い
Na
な
2245 Oh 8 and Eja, let's discard 3 cards leaving 2.
2245ああ8とえじゃ2枚残しで3枚捨てしよう
Or discard 3 cards and press the button for that number of cards with 3 cards discarded.
か3枚捨てオーでえ3枚捨てした状態でえっとその枚数分ボタン
Press as many buttons as you want to press.
押す枚数分ボタンを
Is it okay to press the middle button three times?
押しこの真ん中のボタンでいいの3回トントントンあいいのか
1223 Are you coming here?
1223これで来んのか来い
Oh here it is
あ来たこれ
is 2 pairs 2 pairs
は2ペア2ペア
Desu pair
ですツペア
Yay!
だやっ
My brother's guardian is this
たあ弟配人はこれはジ
Hey, it's here. It's interesting.
かあここにあるんだえ面白あごめんこう
No matter what, this is my victory
かどうだこれ僕の勝ち
It's my victory. Four people can do this.
か僕の勝ちだあこれ4人でできるん
is
だ
When you're done, break it up and give it back.
で終ったら壊して返すの
Put it in when finished
か終わったら入れ
After a few seconds, turn off the lever and press the right lever.
て何秒か経ったらレバーを切って右のレバー
Put 12345
12345入れてで
Well, which one?
えっとどっちだ
Shuffle left here
左ここでシャッフルし
After a few seconds of shuffling, turn off the lever and press the right lever for 5 seconds.
てシャッフルされてる何秒か経ったらレバーを切ってでえっと右のレバーを5秒
Moderate
ほどにする
1345 This is the end. This is really interesting. What a genius.
1345これで終わりとえこれマジでおもろいねいやすごい天才だ
Wow, everyone made 1234 games in one week. So far, it's amazing.
よすごいな1週間でみんなゲームを1234つ作ったよ今のとこいやすごいよ
I'm looking forward to it. I've made 4 games in a week. That's awesome.
期待してるよこれから1週間で4つ作ったんだよゲームやば
I'll probably do it at an RPG school or something.
いって多分なんかRPGスクールとかでやる
This Minecraft game is more difficult than this, with its crazy ceilings and complicated work.
よりむずいよこのマイクラのゲームはこれややばいな天井とかも凝ってるし仕事がね
too fast
早すぎる
Oh ghost, ghost
おお化けが化けが
Okay, let's go to the introduction corner. Wait a minute, before that.
いるえじゃあ紹介コーナー行きますかあいやちょっと待ってその前
Let's go take a look at the foundation of the digital circus I created last week.
にあれを見に行こう先週僕がね作ったデジタルサーカスのね土台をねちょっと
Another listener took over, check it out.
別のリスナーさんが引き継いでくれたんだよそれ見に
Let's go, the roof is done. I only did the foundation and walls.
行こううお屋根ができてるこのね土台と壁だけは僕がやったんだ
But I was looking forward to it.Wait, I'm making both sides too.
けどちょ楽しみにしてたんだよえあ待って両側も作ってん
Are you going to see Janja?
じゃんじゃ見に行きますか
Wow, you did a great job on the ceiling.
うおーすげえ天井やばよくやったな僕この周りの
I was the only one who could use World Edit on the walls, so I did that, but the ceiling was also pokopoko by myself.
壁は僕だけワールドエデト使えるからそれでやったけど天井だって1人でポコポコ
You did it, you did it in one week, it's amazing
やったんでしょこれ1週間でやったのやばすぎ
Wait, Rhett too.
でしょああれはまさかポモあ待ってレットも
The reproducibility is too high
あるやば再現度高高すぎ
This is the world and this is the exit.
でしょほんまにこれワールでこれね出口
and
と
That's amazing, but it probably means I can go left and right.
すげえでもさこれ多分左左右行けるってことじゃあれだ
I didn't expect this to mean that a room was created in this position.
これまさかさこの位置は部屋を作ったってことじゃないの
Did you make a room?
かこれ部屋作ったでしょ
It's so thin, it's so amazing, it's serious, each and every one of us should make it properly
うすげえすげえこれマジでえあ1人1人ちゃんと作っ
I wonder where it is?
てるどこだっけあここまさか
Oh there's a bug
ああバグってるや
That's amazing, I used Ed crystal to express the eyes.
ばすごいあなるほどねこれエドクリスタルで目を表現したん
Kae: I guess this other room was made based on a prediction.
かえ他のこの部屋とかあ多分これ予想で作ったんか
Maybe you predicted all of this.
な多分これ全部予想でやったでしょ
Amazing reproducibility
すご再現度高
Sugiyabai stage and other things
すぎやばいステージのところとかやばいもん
Naza Amazing Digital
なザアメイジングデジタル
The circus is crazy, I'm glad I left it to this.
サーカスやばいやマジ任せてよかったあこれはこれ
This is the last scene, where the mouth is limp.
はこれね最後のシーンだね口ぐにゃーのとこ
This is the scene where Neguchi is squishy. Now, sit down.
ね口ぐにゃーのシーンのとこだよさて座ってるえ
[Music] Wow, this is the best YouTube
[音楽]すごこれ何かの最これはねYouTube
If you search for The Amazing Digital Circus, you'll see 3D animation now.
でザアメイジングデジタルサーカスで検索すると出るなんか3Dアニメーション今
That's amazing, it's been played about 100 million times in 3 weeks.
すごいよ3週間で1億再生ぐらいされてるやつなんだ
But it's a mix of cute anime and a bit of Back Rooms and SCP.
けど可愛いアニメとちょっとバックルームズとかSCP混じっ
It's a creepy work with horror elements, but my listeners probably all
てるようなホラー要素のある不気味な作品なんだけどうちのリスナーさん多分みんな
I love it, it's amazing, I want you to make that too.
好きだよいやすごいなえじゃあれも作ってほしい
Beyond my exit, beyond my exit
わこの出口の先出口の先
Please come this way and connect to the entrance here.
させっかくだからこっち来てここの入口に繋がるように
Well, that's what I was trying to do.
してよこっから一応ね僕がねやろうとしてたのはねほら
Wait there, connect from around here, do your best, and I'll help too.
そこに待てかここら辺から繋げてちょっとか頑張って僕も手伝う
But let's try our best to connect until we get to that circus.
けどそこのサーカスまで行くまでちょこ頑張って繋げよう
Ma told me about that office, so I looked at it and it was amazing.
あのオフィスのところをマが言ってたから見てけどめっちゃ
It was interesting, it was interesting, and it looked good. I thought everyone would like it.
面白かった面白いしよそうなんだよみんな好きかなと思ってた
But I'll do my best to connect this place.It's like this.
けど頑張ってここね繋げるんだこことかさこうなってる
If there's a place you can go to, like a furnace, let's connect.
かまどっかね行けそうなところあったら繋げよう
No, I understand that the work is really hard.
いや作業大変分かるマジ大変だ
Okay, now it's time for digestion.
よしじゃあ消化タイムに入ります
Well, I've just been looking through it, and I wonder if there's anything new.
か今は僕がねざっくり見てなんか新しいの増えてるかなで見たやつだけどこっ
Well, there's actually something here.
からいやここに実はあるんすよみたいなのがあっ
Come on.
たら来て
Give it to me, this is a circus. Oh yeah, it's probably a circus.
くれえこれサーカスだよねあそうだね多分このはサーカスだよ
It's all white, so why don't you take me with you?
な真っ白なんだおじゃあ連れてってもらおうか
Not good
ないい
There's a pool at that hotel.
よプールありますよどこあのさっきのホテルの
Tokoro Tsuki
ところつい
I'm climbing up the sky, but
てこう空を登っていくえけどあ
Climb, climb, new successes, are they increasing?
た登れ登れ新しい成功もあ増えてるかもう成功
Mart is good, the number of successful marts has increased tremendously.
マートはいいよ成功マートめっちゃ増え
Terua Hotel
てるあホテルえ
Where is this top?
どここっち上
I didn't see it
か見てなかっ
When you think of a hotel, you think of a pool.
たやっぱホテルと言ったらプール
Isn't that right?
でしょえあこの
I won't fall into the safety pool ahead.
先安全プールもう落ちない
Oh, I won't forget that a falling accident happened. Someone disappeared.
おお落下事故発生忘れない誰かなくなっ
It's a pool. What's this?
てるあプールだあえ何これ
Gachipur
ガチプール
This is good
じゃんこれいい
There's something a little scary about that, like a Jizo statue.
なでもなんかあれだなちょっと怖いなお地蔵さんとか置いてある
The pool is full of suspiciousness [music]
プール怪しさ満点[音楽]
Why is the back side blocked like this?
のなんで後ろ側こうやって塞がれてん
No, it's bigger
のいやもっとでかい
I want a pool.If I can build something like this, it's something like that.
プール欲しいなこういうの作れるならそれこそなんかあのある
What do you call it, not Summer Jumbo? It's a big one for kids.
じゃんサマージャンボじゃなくてなんて言うんだ子供用のでかい
Anywhere in the pool?
プールどっかもうでも
I don't want space, but there's more than you might think.
スペースいやでも意外とあるよみんなまだまだあるから
Let's make the next one
作ろう次な
Summerland, yes, Summerland-like Summer-Summer Jumbo is that.
方サマーランドそうサマーランドみたいなサマーサマージャンボはあれ
It's a lottery. Maybe it's gone.
だ宝くじだあもういないもしかして
I'm sure you're here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm sure it's the end
コシブ終わりあいるあ来た来た来た来たあれあでも君確か
You're an SCP person, right? The SCP Foundation isn't here yet.
SCPの人だよねSCP財団まだ
I think there's still something
あるまだ何かあるよう
Dako Nakaa Museum of Art has new exhibits at Okeo
だこの中あ美術館新しい展示品があるオオケオ
Okay ah, I'm here. Everyone is looking for people who want to make it. Behind the scenes.
オッケーああ来たよみんな作りたい人募集後ろに
Connect the hallways and make it as you like. Make this everyone.
廊下をつなげて好きに作ってくださいこれみんな作って
Please, this foundation facility was expanded and advertised. Thank you, I don't understand.
くださいこの財団施設ね伸ばして宣伝でしたありがとういやわかんねえな
But it would certainly be better to put more signboards around here instead of over there.
でも確かにあそこじゃなくてもっとここら辺に看板置いといた方が
I guess it was good, I guess so too.
良かったんじゃないかいいな僕もなんか
Let's build it If you are confident, expand the SCP foundation facilities.
作ろう皆さんも自信ある方SCPの財団施設を広げ
Let's advertise it.
ましょう宣伝でし
The next person
た次の方
Go ahead, that big building you just saw.
どうぞえなんかさっきでかい建物
Ai Aretsuki
あいあれつい
Tekouun
てこうん
That pole dance
あのポールダンスのところの
I didn't see anyone here tomorrow.
人あしたえここってさいや見なかったっ
I feel like I've seen a lot of them
けここここ見た気がするぞ増え
This is scary BGM and I saw this voice.
たこれ怖いBGMだしこのね声見たな
I didn't introduce piano streaming.
ピアノ配信紹介してなかったっ
The atmosphere here, where Keko is tied to a mysterious chest, is really nice.
けこの謎のくりにね繋がれてるここマジ雰囲気いいな
No, I'm going to get off if something happens.
いや何かあるのか降りる
I haven't introduced you.
かあ紹介してなかっ
Takore
たこれ
[Music] has never been like this before.
[音楽]はまでもこんな感じかあしてなかった
Well, I guess I saw it by myself. It's amazing.
じゃあ僕多分ね1人で見たんだこれすごいよ
Hey, I love mysterious spaces like this, so that's why I'm watching this.
ねこういう謎空間僕大好きだからえだから僕ねこれ見
I made that, oh thank you. Look at this, I copied it too.
てあれ作ったんだおおありがとうこれ見ていや僕もなんか真似し
I thought so and made it
ようって思って作ったんだ
What I made next is
よこ作ったのは
[Music] Where is that?
[音楽]あれどこ
But wait a minute.
だどこだちょっと待ってあれ
This is it
だこれ
Hey, when I look at that space, I try to imitate the pure white sky and red.
ねあの空間見て僕もなんか真似して真っ白の空に赤い
I made a door
扉作ったんだ
It's like cyberpunk, right? [Music]
よサイバーパンクみたいでしょそうなんだ[音楽]
Alright then, next [music]
よよしそれでは次の[音楽]
The BGM plays something like how many different Minecraft songs are there?
方BGMねなんかマイクラ曲全何種類みたいなやつを流し
Surprisingly, there is no referral tax today.You are the person who introduces me.
てる今日は意外とあれか紹介税がいない感じか君は紹介の人
It looks like it's different [music]
か違うっぽい[音楽]
Introducing
な紹介する
I'm not the creator, but it looks like a huge castle behind the back wall of the Chinese building.
制作者じゃないけど中華建物の裏側の壁の奥にあるえそうなんかでかい城みたいの
That's right. How do we get there? Shall we go?
あったやつだよねあどうやって行くんだろうあついてこうか
Na
な
There are a lot of people over there who are still working on it.
向こうまあとそう作りかけの人も多いしな
[Music] What's up there, that UFO?
[音楽]上に何があるんだああのUFO
[Music] Kakore
[音楽]かこれ
A row of heads coming from a cat
ねこっから入るあ並んでる頭
But what is the concept behind this UFO?
がこのこのUFOのコンセプトは何あ
Amazing where did it come in?
すごいどっから入っ
The octopus's alien head is glowing
たこの宇宙人といい頭光ってる
But the concept of this and that is a mystery
けどこれこれのコンセプトが謎あでも内装
good length
いい長の
Nekyaku is also the creator, but there is a mini story, so I'll show you after the museum if you'd like.
ね教会も制作者ですがミニストーリーがあるので美術館の後によければ案内します
I think it's hard to understand in the comments, but you said something about Asoka Art Museum.
コメントでは分かりづらいかと思うあそっか美術館なんか言ってた
Look at that alien concept thing.
なそこね宇宙人のコンセプトのやつを見て
from
から
I see
おおなるほど
It looks like you, so I just made it. I see.
それ出てるぶわんブワブワンって出てる君ぽいから作っていただけですなるほど
The guys on the top are kind of cute
上の奴らが上の奴らがなんかね可愛く
Even in UF, there are a lot of Kim Mirai types at the top.
てUFでもねやっぱ上は金未来系が多いと
happy
嬉しい
Hey, it's this big!
なあこんなでかかったっ
It was hard to understand the sense of art at first.
けで美術感があれか美術感も最初分かりづらかったからな
increased in rank
位増えた
Apparently now
らしいさて
special room for lambs
小羊のための特別室
Oh, you can donate money here too.
あ献金できるよここでお金も入れて
Yes, I saw this.November 9, 2023, in the unnamed exhibition room.
あるえこれ見たやつ僕あ2023年11月9未名展示室にて
Toka's body was found and the investigation revealed it and it became a hot topic.
遺体が見つかりましたそはの調査により明らかとなり大きな話題をびましたトカは
Try to understand the feelings that led this small artist to leave Renomu in the exhibition room. Disposal of Kagami's body.
この小さな芸術家が己れのむを展示室に残すに至った心情を試みえ鏡遺体の処理
We decided to preserve the situation at that time with a replica of Gomoji's old age.
ごも何性の老性のレプリカにて当時の状況を保全することとしまし
Because the situation is a delicate one, such as the death of someone who has died, the interference may cause discomfort to the person being interfered with.
た人の死というデリケートな事情であるため干渉ななされた方に不快感をもたらす
Although there is a possibility, I would appreciate it if you could use it.
可能性もございますがなりとぞご用しいただければ幸いですまたトカを運営して
The Kuron Foundation has established a private fund to prevent similar areas from occurring in the future.
おります空論財団では今後同様の地帯が起きることを防ぐべく個基金を設立しまし
We are accepting donations at the same time in the fight box on the right. Regarding the authority of this matter,
た危険の寄付献金は右の喧嘩箱にて同時に受けつけておりますなお本件の権威につき
Moreover, it is published on Mei's YouTube channel.
ましては飯のYouTubeチャンネルにて公開されております
ah
ああ
Thank you, I'll put some money in.30
ありがとうじゃ金入れとくか30
Coins have also increased separately from this.
コインさてえでもこれとは別に増えたってこと
Right, this is what I saw in my dream.
でしょこれじゃね夢で見た
room
部屋
I never thought my name would appear in my dreams, this or that, or that child's room.
まさか夢にやこれあれかあの子の部屋か名前が出てこ
No switch child eh
ないスイッチの子えあ
No way
まさか
It’s so amazing, how did you express it like this?
うおおうだなるほどねこうやって表現したのか
That's really good Po
めっちゃいいじゃんあポ
Even Nico is sure of this too.Press the switch and it will be confirmed.
ニコでもこれも確定なんだねスイッチ押したら確定
Well, the windows are nice too, but it's kind of creepy.
でいや窓もいいななんか不気味
And I was scared even in my dreams
で夢にも怖かったもん
Others are sheep
な他はあ羊
It's not done yet. Someone can make it for me.
ねここまだできてないよ誰か作ってもいい
This is a mystery.
ぞこれ謎これ
amazing
すごい
I feel like going home
はあな感じか帰り
Masuhai
ますはい
Actually, there was someone who offered to show me around the church, so I guess it's okay.
ほんじゃあなんか教会案内してくれるって人がいたからまとっか
I'll wait, but the bottom part is really crowded.
な待ちますいやでも下部分はもマジで密集してん
Na
な
3, so we can't explore the lower part in one day.
3だから下部分の探索はもうね1日じゃ不
It's so possible that it's truly amazing, so look at your field of vision.
可能がすぎてマジで圧巻だよだから視野とかをさほら
If you do this, you'll end up saying something dangerous, so don't do it.
こうするとやばいしょり言っちゃうからやんない
But at least this much
けどこぐらいにし
[music]
[音楽]
Oh, the church people
てあ教会の人は
I won't know where I am unless you show me around.
案内してくれないと僕どこだかわかんないよ
There was a restaurant right below the museum, and I went to the ruins right below it to hide it.
え美術館の真下の方にレストランがあってその直直下に隠すように途端の廃墟に行っ
Please, yes, yes, museum
てくださいはいはいはいはい美術館
is that or that
があれかあれの
The master is around here
マスタここら辺にある
Where is it like?
らしいどこ
Well, you made this well too.
だいやこれもよく作ってくれた
If there are no people who can make a lot of the same thing, the project won't work.
よこういう同じものをたくさん作ってくれる人がいなければ企画が成り立たない
Thank you very much for making it all over the wall.
から助かってるよもっと壁一面に作ってくれた
Previously this
前これ
It's simple, it's amazing, it's quite difficult to make these stairs.
かこれ単純いやこれすごいないやこの階段作んの結構大変なんだ
It's a special block so it's really
よ特殊なブロックだからめっちゃ
It's around here even if it's off.
ずれるえでもここら辺だよな
Maybe somewhere higher up?
多分どこだもっと上の方か
It's on the same wall.
な同じ壁の面にあります1周目の配信でいらしてくれていたお
shop
店
Where is it?
ですどこだ
restaurant restaurant
レストランレストラン
It's not like that restaurant.
レストランあこれじゃないもんねだって
There are ruins at the bottom [music]
下の方廃墟があっ[音楽]
I can't find it
てやば見つから
No Matsuya ah
ない松屋あっ
This is where the art museum is. This is the museum.
てえ美術館ってここだよなこの美術館のだよ
Hey, this is the place I just saw full of grass.
ね今見てた草だらけのところここ
Or maybe
かそれとも
I'm sleepy trying to figure out who's here.
こっち誰れださ探すのがねむずいわ
Is this where the bottom grows?
下が生えてるところあこれか
[music]
[音楽]
The same side, the same side means this or that.
な同じ面同じ面ってことはこっちかあこれじゃ
Maybe this is it
ね多分これだ
You've already seen this restaurant. You've seen this stylish restaurant.
これでも見たよねここのレストランこのおしゃれレストラン見
Takore's
たこれの
This is coming soon
近くこれ
It's a different color
かえ違うよ
I'm not sure what to do
なあれどれた全然
I wonder if someone will guide me like that?
ああんなにかもしかして案内してくれるのかどっか
I understand
分かる
here
こっち
This, this, this, this.
こっちあこれこれ
I'll watch Kaja
かじゃ見ます
picture
え
Yes, you're making something outrageous, what is this?
はいもうとんでもないもん作ってんな何これ
It's Dark Souls, it's Arron.
ダークソウルじゃんえあのアルロンだえあ
No, the front entrance is so plain that I don't understand it without Ebardet.
えバールデットなしでいや正面入り口地味すぎてわかんないっ
hand
て
You did a great job with World Edit.
ワールドエディットのしでよくやったな
Awesome mini-story: A dilapidated shop hidden in a restaurant
すごミニストーリーありえ美術官加法レストランに隠された途端のボロ屋
You can watch it first
にてえ先に見ていい
Noisy
のすご
A church is like a castle.
教会ってかもう城城だ
Okay, let's see
よじゃあ見る
Or the rags hidden in the restaurant under the museum.
か美術館の下のレストランに隠された途端のボロやはあ
Okay, let's go. You made something outrageous again.
はん行きますかまたとんでもないもん作ったな
that
それ
This is it [music]
がこれ[音楽]
This or that restaurant is different from this restaurant.
かレストランのあ違うこれかレストラン
rags on the verge of
の途端のボロ
It's probably this one, around here, this one.
屋多分これだなここら辺だこれか
What's wrong?
な違うか
I think it's around here.
な途端ここら辺だと思うんだけど
What is this ramen and the ridiculous amount of ramen?
なこれラーメンや途端のボロ
It's right below the restaurant.This is the restaurant.This is it.This is definitely this.
やレストランの真下だもんなレストランこれでしょあこれだ絶対これ
da [music]
だ[音楽]
This is it
これだ
Oh, it's someone's dead body. This town feels familiar.
おお誰かの死体だもうなんか見慣れたこの街
Because I'm used to seeing it
で見慣れてしまったから
Hey, something is about to begin again. We've finally arrived here.
なあったさあまた何かが始まろうとしているえようやくこの地に到着したこのここ
The relationship with Japan has been deteriorating for several years, but somehow we have managed to share the teachings of our God with the people of this land.
数年我が国との関係性は悪化していたがどうにかこの地の人間にも我が神の教えを
The harshness of the piercing gaze that I want to convey is something that can't be helped for now, so I demand it first.
伝えたい突き刺さる視線の厳しさは今はまだ仕方ないものとして需要するまずは
The descendants of those who settled this land when it was once a valid nation.
かつての有効国だった時代にこの地に入植したものの子孫たちを
Let's look for it.According to what we've heard, it's said that they're building a magnificent cathedral.
探そう伝え聞く話ではそれはそれは立派な大聖堂を建立しているとのことだ探して
There is no such thing as a street where you can't find it, and what is worrying is that legitimate competitions are taking place after the illegal ones.
見つからぬ通りはあるまい懸念すべきは違法を後において正当なる競技が出して
There is a possibility that if I do not correct it, their faith itself will be corrected.
いる可能性だ私が是正しなければ訂正しなければなる前が彼らの信仰心そのもの
In order to avoid denying the
までを否定することのないようあくまで音便に進めることを
In any case, today the tired military is flying airplanes, but eventually
心がけるいずれにせよ今日は疲れた軍では飛行機なんてものを飛ばしているがいずれ
We civilians will also be able to travel quickly and easily by flying through the sky.
我々民間人も速やかに軽やかに空を飛んで旅ができるのだろう
Days pass by without a search for my compatriots.
かあ同胞の捜索がまらぬまま日が過ぎていく
The enemy of our country is deep-rooted this time, but we can't find it even if we search for the Cathedral of the Steps.
段の聖堂も探せど探せど見つからない我が国への敵は今度に根深いがこちらが懐を
However, when it comes to social activities such as housing contracts and employment, there are walls.
開けば次第に応じてくれるそれでも住居の契約や就職といった社会活動になると壁は
I've lost all the money I have, and the ruins I've washed up on are attacked by insects.
大きい手持ちの金が心持なくなってきた流れ着いた廃墟はは虫と隙間かずに襲わ
This town, which is far from peaceful and full of people, is a place where people can settle.
れるばかりの空間でおよそ安寧とはほど遠いこの町は入植たたえおのためどか
It was difficult, yes, yes, it was cheap, but they should be the same, so why are they excluding me?
困難はいはいはい安物だったのは彼らも同じはずなのになぜ私を排斥するの
Karonen's blood seeps into it and it's readable.
かロねん血が染み込み読め
I finally met someone who has the blood of my country, but he is also not part of the community of my fellow countrymen.
ないようやく我が国の血を引くものに出会っただが彼も同胞のコミュニティには
It's sad that he doesn't seem to understand, but I respect him for living assimilated into the local community.
通じていないようだ悲しいことだが現地に同化して生きる彼のことは尊重し
It's tall or thin, but the clues are impossible to decipher.There's a ramen shop in the neighborhood, but there's a sign on top of it.
たいかか細いが手がかり解読不能だ近所のラーメ屋があるがその上に
The angel who seems to have a shop selling snacks and bars is of Japanese descent.
スナックだスナックだかバーだかの店があるらしいその天使が我が国の血を引く者
Let's visit her tomorrow as she is said to be the face of our company.
たちの顔役とのことだった明日彼女を訪れてみよう
Although she was able to contact Oni Angel, she was only a community of descendants of early settlers.
おに天使に接触することはできたが彼女はあくまで初期入植者の子孫をコミュニティ
He seems to think of him as a member of the group, but he gave me hints about how many times he met the giant with a large mouth under the bridge of the dragon.
の仲間とみなしているようだヒントはくれたものの何回竜の橋の下大口の巨人
Thank you for everything you look at
見つめる先よりひありをえ
Oh man, even when I look back at the sentences I wrote down, there's no meaning to them.
あヒトだなあメモした文章を見返しても意味が
Speaking of unknown dragons, I remember seeing a giant face intact.
分からない龍といえば巨大な顔の無事を見かけた覚えがある
I arrived quickly, but the inside of the cathedral was filled with an eerie silence, with no sign of anyone.
がやだやくたどり着いただが大聖堂の中は人の気配もなく不気味の静寂に満ちている
Considering the relationship between the two countries, what was hidden in such a place was being suppressed.
あんな場所に隠されていたのは両国の両国の関係を思えば弾圧されていたの
After returning home, I remembered that in many cases, cathedrals have an underground section.
だろう家に帰ってから思い出したが多くの場合聖堂には地下が設けられるといううん
He may have been hiding in the basement and praying, just like my uncle used to do.
えは地下にこもって祈りを捧げていたのかもしれない私の叔父がよくしていたよう
In addition to distracting myself by converting the feelings that cannot be described as anger or sadness into words, which I feel as if my pen is heavy.
に筆が重く感じる怒りとも悲しみともつかぬ感情を文字に転化して気を紛らわす他
It is a common story all over the world that local gatherings and beliefs change as a result, and I am fully aware of this as well.
ない現地の集合と信仰と集合し変化することは世界中よくある話で私もそれは十分
I knew this, but this is too much of an evil thing.
承知していたがこれはいくらなんでもあまりに宿悪
It's my struggle with God, it's a problem before that, and I'm satisfied with words like differences in ideology.
だ我が神への苦労イナそれ以前の問題だ思想の違いなどなどといった言葉で納得
Maybe someday they'll find a good victim. What about the sheep?
できようか彼らはやがていつかおしい犠牲者を見出すだろう羊がどうだとかわけの
I don't think he wants to be told something he doesn't understand.
わからない話をされたがろなものではなさそうだ
Yeah, there's a field of vision behind the white rose underground
うん地下白いバラの裏に視界が
red
赤いう
Well, first of all, I found this just because it's Hirie.
えっとまずひりえだからでもこれ見つけたんだよ
Na
な
Probably probably
きっと多分だ
But the dragon
けど竜の
A giant with a big mouth The giant stares at the tip
大口でえ巨人巨人の見つめる先ひり
of
の
Hirie, I cheated and found it.
ひりえじゃ僕ずるして見つけたの
A church that I couldn't find for a long time when it was here.
かでここにあるとずっと見つからなかった教会
was here
がここにあったん
What an amazing place
だすごいな地
Or underground, or underground.
か地下いやでも地下への
There's nothing like the entrance.
入り口それっぽいものはないな
white
白い
Here's what's weird
バ怪しいのはここら辺
Somehow I can go
かなんかどうにかしたら行けると
Behind the scenes, solve the mystery
かゾの裏側さあて謎解き
Let's look for it, everyone.
だ探すぞみんな
No, it's a big deal, so don't fly away
いやせっかくだから飛ばないで
Let's look for the giant with a big mouth
探そうあ大口の巨人
That's Mr.
ってどうもさんの
First of all, go upstairs
ことまずは上に行って
Let's see it
みようわすご
Okay
よし
Amakou
あまこう
It wasn't Katoomoore.
かとおでもあれだななかったな
There's got to be an underground entrance somewhere, but finding it is the fun part.
どっかに地下の入り口があるはずなんだがあ探すのも醍醐だから
No, it's amazing, really
ないやすごいよ本当
Kanaeko is amazing from the inside.
にないねやっぱ中からかなえこのさすごく
Not a great decoration
ないすごいよ装飾
What's amazing? [Music]
がすごいな何[音楽]
Should I read that again? I brought a book, please.
あれ読み直すかあ本持ってきた頼むあ本
I guess that's true. There's no other way than that. Wait a minute.
あるないかそうだよなあの卒しかないもんなちょっと待っ
Teroe didn't give me any hints.
てろえでもなんかヒントなかったよ
That's what I said
なそれといった
Hint, this time I'll search by myself
ヒントちょ今回こそ僕ちゃんと1人で探す
I'm going to borrow a little bit of this book, that punishment.
わちょっと借りるわちょこの本あのおしおし
If you roll your mouse hard enough, you can copy it.
みんなマウスのコロコロをぎゅってやるとねコピーできる
From hobby
からホビーし
While looking at Takore
たこれを見ながら
let's do it
やろう
Well, I already found this somewhere in town.
さて街かのところこれはもう見つけ
Even if you say that the underground system is being destroyed, I don't think there are any hints about the underground.
たうんうんうん制度に地下がけられというえでも地下のヒント別にないもんなあ
A white rose behind a white rose
白いバラの裏に白いバラの
The white background
裏白いバを
Let's look for this, isn't this?
探そうこれじゃないよねこれは
No, it's a flower after all. Let's look for a flower. This is probably this.
違うやっぱ花なんだ花を探そうこれだ多分これ
It's here, white
だよ来た白い
Rose, white flower
バラ白い花あれ
Ha, this is also a white rose.
はあこれも白いバラだ
There was, there was, there was, there was, there was, there was.
なあったあったあったあったあったあったあったあっ
Where did this open?
たこれでどこが開いたん
And the other side too
だ向こうも
be
ある
Isn't this all or this something opened?
これだけかこれでどこかが開いたんじゃない
Kaa
かあ
It's amazingly good
すごよし引きます
[music]
[音楽]
cormorant
う
I'm praying here
ここで祈りを捧げてい
Ta
た
So what were you doing when your vision was red?
で視界が赤い何してたんだ
Okay, but unlike the other statues, the color is darker.
よしかもほら他の像と違って色が黒ずんでる
It was horror, but there was an ax [music]
ホラーだったやっぱり斧があっ[音楽]
It looks similar to the sheep room. Was it the same ritual?
て羊の部屋似てるね同じ儀式だったんか
Wow, that's amazing. There's nothing else like it.
なやっぱすごいなえ他ないよ
There's nothing else hidden [music]
ね他何かが隠されてるとかはないよ[音楽]
You made a good space
ねや空間よく作った
That's all.
な以上ですいや
Thank you, this is seriously amazing. This gimmick is also amazing.
ありがとうマジですごいわこれのギミックもすごい
It's closed. It's closed.
しあ閉じてる閉じ
Teru
てる
Okay
よし
Okay, let's add a shadow at the end.
じゃあま最後に影も入れる
Also include shadows
か影も入れ
I guess I'll just look around and call it a day. I'm really going to do a lot of things in a week, everyone.
て周り見て終わりにしよっかな本当になんか1週間でよくやるよみんな
Seriously, I can't even open the selfie box.
マジでセルカボックスもねなんか開けなかっ
Ta
た
There are too many producers, so if anyone sees this stream and wants to make something, please see the summary below.
わプロが多すぎるでねこの配信見て僕も何か作りたいっていう人がいたら下の概要
I'll send you the ID from Google Hoom in the column.
欄のねGoogleフームからID送ってく
If you send me your bad ID, I will add it to the whitelist. Thank you.
くさいID送ってくれたらホワイトリストにね追加しますのでよろしくお願いします
If someone can't get in even though I sent them their ID, it's probably
でID送ったのに入れないって人がいたらおそらく
There is a possibility that that ID is different, so please be sure to send your Minecraft ID.
あのIDが違う可能性がありますのでちゃんとねマイクラ内のIDを送って
Please, it's amazing! White [Music]
くださいすごいって白[音楽]
This is nice and done properly
これナイスもちゃんとしてたしね
It's really cool and amazing
かっこいいガチですごい
It's seriously amazing
なマジですごいよ
With this, everyone, I will end this article here.
これということで皆さん今回はこれにて終わりにさせていただきます
Eh, the difference between Minecraft and Minecraft will be one month next week. Just because it's one month doesn't mean we're going to do anything.
え来週でマイクラマイクラ差は1ヶ月ですま1か月だからで言って何かをするわけで
I'll probably introduce it again soon, but from now on, I'll be able to take advantage of my free time and introduce my favorite architecture.
もなく多分また紹介するかと思いますが今後ともね好きな時間に入って好きな建築
If you could actually build it with due consideration to the surrounding buildings.
をしてで本当になんか周りのね方の建築物にね経緯を払って建築していただければ
I don't care what kind of architecture you want, so I'd appreciate your help.
どんな建築をしても構いませんのでよろしくお願いし
Me too, I log in every day and create something, so I'm just going to chat.
ます僕もね一応毎日ログインして何かしらのものは作っているのでただえチャットに
I can't respond outside of the broadcast, so please only respond there.
は配信外以外では反応できませんのでそこだけよろしくお願いし
With that in mind, I would like to end today with this.
ますそんな感じで今日はこれにて終わりにさせていただきたいと思いますご視聴
Thank you to the person who introduced me and the person who always makes it.
ありがとうございました紹介してくださった方えいつも作ってくださってる方
Thank you very much, please respect your manners. I'm very happy. So, tomorrow.
ありがとうございますマナー守ってねとても嬉しいですということでえー明日は
It's a ghost photo. I'd like to see a ghost photo for the first time in a while. See you again tonight.
心霊写真です心霊写真を久しぶりに見たいと思いますまた夜お会いしましょう以上
Thank you for your hard work
ですお疲れ
Subscribe to Samootto channel, follow and archive highly rated Twitter
様おっとチャンネル登録高評価Twitterのフォローとアーカイブに
Thank you for your feedback and comments
感想コメントよろしくお願いし
Masu
ます